ukjobsnet.com 2015-12-29

# Privacy Policy for UK Jobs Network

## 1\. Introduction

> This policy covers the use of personal information that Online Classifieds Limited collect when you use this web site.
> 
> THIS POLICY DOES NOT COVER THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION OTHER WEB SITES MAY COLLECT ABOUT YOU. This web site contains links to other web sites where they may be of interest to You. Given that these are separate sites we are NOT responsible for their content, security or information collecting policies or availability. You should therefore visit the other site's privacy, terms and conditions and relevant disclaimers.
> 
> We are committed to keeping your personal information private and only collecting and using information in accordance with the Data Protection Act and this policy.
> 
> This privacy policy is updated from time to time and may have been updated since your last visit. Please familiarise yourself with our Privacy Policy whenever you submit information to this site.

## 2\. What we collect and who we share it with

> In order to track online traffic flows we record anonymous statistical data.  
>  This data may include the pages visited, browser type and IP address.  
>  We may use this data for marketing, security or any other purposes and Online Classifieds Limited may share this information with any 3rd party in the execution of these tasks. 
> 
> If you would like to have your personal data removed or updated from our records, please notify us using the "Contact Us" page or write to us at the address below. 
> 
> If you would like to have your personal data removed from our records, please notify us using the "Contact Us" page or write to us at the address below. 

## 3\. Our use of Cookies

> A cookie is a small amount of data sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it. To protect your privacy, your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.
> 
> We may use temporary cookies to track and/or store anonymous data.
> 
> You may choose to reject cookies from this web site in your web browsing software. If you reject cookies from this site, some areas of this site that require the use of cookies may not be accessible to you.

## 4\. Access to your personal information

> Under the Data Protection Act, you have the right to request a copy of the personal information Online Classifieds Limited holds about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. We charge £10 for information requests.
> 
> Please address requests to:
>
>> The Data Protection Officer  
>  Online Classifieds Limited  
>  250 Derwent House  
>  RTC Business Park  
>  London Road  
>  Derby  
>  DE24 8UP  
>  United Kingdom  
> 
> 
> If You are aged 16 or under, please get your parent/guardian's permission beforehand whenever You provide personal information through this web site.
